bebuzeeadbuz.com 2019-04-25

# Privacy Policy - Bebuzee Adbuz| Legal Terms & Use |

## Bebuzee Privacy Policy

[Bebuzee.com](https://www.bebuzee.com/) has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of visitors to our site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Bebuzee.com, and any other website through which we conduct business. 

### Information We Collect and Our Use and Disclosure of Your Information.

* * *

We may collect the following information: 

  * Name, email address, city.

We require this information in order to communicate with you effectively 

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We will use this information to send promotional e-mails about special offers
  * We may use this information for internal research and analysis
  * We will never pass your details on to a third party unless required by law to do so

We use cookies on certain pages of our site. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most cookies are "session cookies" which means that they are automatically deleted at the end of each session. A cookie itself does not have the ability to automatically collect personal information about you. A cookie can store certain information that identifies your computer to us so that you don't have to re-enter information as frequently when you use our site. 

### Linked Sites

* * *

For your convenience, this site contains links to other sites. Bebuzee.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

### Security

* * *

This site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All user information stored on our server is stored in an encrypted format. Notwithstanding these efforts, we caution you that "perfect security" does not exist on the internet. 

### Choice/Opt-Out

* * *

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

### Contacting Bebuzee.com

* * *

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can [contact us](https://www.bebuzeeadbuz.com/contact-us). 

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
